Oh!
Evening! What's up, Senpai?
Uh...
Senpai?
Sorry this is out of the blue, Uzaki.
What is?
Please: be with me. I need you.
Huh?
Senpai...
Uh, hey.
Hey, hi.
Sorry. I know this is sudden.
It's okay.
Um, you asked me to be with you?
On the phone?
Yeah, about that...
Huh?
I just can't seem
to bring myself to go in alone!
Come with me to the cat café!
Thank God you're here! I mean it!
Oh, wow, I can't wait!
This is my first time--I'm so nervous!
Ow! What--hey! Quit kicking--ow!
Stop! Cut it out! That hurts!
Party of two?
Take off your shoes and go on inside.
Wow... cats!
They have cats, Uzaki!
Yep. They have cats, all right.
Well, duh. We are a cat café.
I... I can touch them, right?
Calm down, Senpai. You've got those scary eyes.
If the cats are okay with it,
go right ahead and pet them gently.
Got it.
Do it like I taught you earlier: from below.
Uh, right.
Whoa...
Now's your chance! Cats like being scratched
under their chins or behind their ears.
O-Okay.
Uzaki, look! A cat--on my lap!
Yes, yes. Good for you.
But don't be too loud, or it'll run away.
Wow. Creepy.
He doesn't get this excited around humans.
All that gloominess must be
keeping some stuff repressed.
Cootchie, cootchie, coo...
He's so creepy that I don't even mind
the extremely misleading way
he got me here in the first place.
He's too overjoyed for words.
Hey, Uzaki, what's with that plastered-on smile?
Just thinking how creepy it is that
you act so cool, but you like cute things.
Say what? Jerk.
Whoops. My true feelings slipped out.
Why, you...
It's also creepy that you're careful
to speak quietly so as not to spook the cats.
Figures!
Hey, your true feelings are showing again.
But I am glad you came today.
I'd get to the entrance and do a U-turn.
You're exaggerating.
I've got to thank you somehow.
Thank me?
Yeah. Anything come to mind?
Hmm... let's see...
Well, my birthday's actually coming up soon.
I'm turning 20, so I'd like to make it sorta special.
So, uh...
Sorry, Uzaki.
Huh?
Truth is...
Uh... yes?
My legs are so numb that
I haven't processed anything you've said.
Can you repeat that?
Then get rid of the cat!
No way!
If you can't have a conversation,
we'll just move it.
But it was finally on my lap!
Just a little longer?
Uncross your legs already
and get those pins and needles out.
It's not a quick-fix kind of thing...
Ow, ow, ow...
Oh!
Poke!
Cut that out! What the hell? Idiot!
You were just so wide open,
you were practically asking for it!
Yeah, right! Everybody's wide open
when their legs are numb!
Not so loud, now--you'll scare the kitty-cats!
Poke!
Pokety poke!
Pokety, pokety poke-poke-poke!
Pokety, pokety, pokety, pokety poke!
Oh, jeez, what now? This is really fun!
This might just awaken something in me!
Uzaki... please... uncle...
Hmm? I can't hear you!
What color is your blood?!
Save that kind of play for home, please.
"Play"?!
Phew, what a blast!
Wasn't that fun, Senpai?
The first half was. Then you got us thrown out!
Dammit. Next time I'll go alone.
Probably can't go back there, though.
And whose fault is that?
Gotta love cat cafés, though.
Lots of friendly kitties!
Right? They were so used to being around people.
It's Very Easy Mode.
"Your communication level is puny.
Level 5? Too bad."
And they still warmed up to you!
So I'm a gun-toting old man now?
I have cats at home, but it's good
to interact with different cats sometimes.
Huh! Must be nice.
Is this what married men
who go to cabaret clubs feel like?
Beats me! What a horrible analogy.
See you later, Senpai!
Yep. I owe you one for today,
so think it over, okay?
Oh, I've already thought that over.
And?
Like I mentioned earlier,
my birthday is coming up. August 7th!
I have high hopes, Senpai!
Her birthday...
And that's why...
...she said she has high hopes for her birthday.
So you're in a pickle.
You do seem like you'd
be bad at that kind of thing.
Right.
Anticipating that Sakurai would be bad at this,
then throwing him for a loop
with vague "high hopes"...
She's quite the schemer.
But that comes from the
peculiar mentality of a girl in love
who wants someone to fret over her.
Not that Hana realizes it herself.
Still, any way you look at it...
...we're going to eat this up!
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Do you have any ideas?
I've been thinking...
U-Uzaki...
Flowers, because my name means "flower"?
So you suck at puns, too!
U-Uzaki...
This is totally the wrong size!
Besides, only hotties can get away
with giving a present like this.
U-Uzaki...
Couldn't you have given me
a uTunes card instead?
I want those special-event bonuses!
It feels like anything
I give her will be a bust.
This is getting complicated!
In reality...
He sure doesn't have an eye for flowers.
A placeholder!
Hey, it has multiplayer!
I'll play with you, loner senpai!
Sounds about right.
She'd be happy with anything Sakurai gives her.
I've thought about this
too much--I'm just so confused.
Then why don't you follow your intuition?
My intuition?
Give her the first thing that came
to mind when you heard "birthday present."
The first thing that came to mind...
Yeah, I still have no idea.
But I need to pick something today.
What's up, Uzaki?
Well, um...
Huh?
I know this is sudden, Senpai.
What is?
I want you to be with me! I need you.
Eh?
I want you to be with me!
What's with Uzaki, anyway?
Oh!
Pub
Senpai!
Uh, hey.
Sorry to spring this on you.
It's okay.
So, um, on the phone...
you said you wanted me to be with you?
About that...
I just couldn't bring myself to go in alone!
Come with me, Senpai!
A... pub?
Your treat! Please?
What for?
I told you, remember? My 20th birthday!
I have high hopes, you know--
for your wallet, that is!
"High hopes"--you mean you were
angling for a pub visit all along?
Yep!
Huh? What's wrong? C'mon, let's go in already!
Hmm?
Are you sure about this?
Celebrating your milestone 20th at a pub?
Oh, totally! I wanted to try drinking with you.
Drinking's fun, right?
That depends on the drinker,
on the circumstances...
No guarantees.
Well, if it's not fun,
you can do something to make it fun!
Now you're being unreasonable.
Let's just enjoy ourselves, okay?
Right.
Ready?
Cheers!
Okay, here goes!
Go on, drink up!
How is it?
Like a soft drink, but also... not.
Does it taste good or what?
There's this, like,
burning in my throat. Deep inside.
Alcohol will do that.
What's beer like?
Want to try?
Uh-huh.
Sorry for the wait!
Enjoy!
Give that a taste.
Whoa!
You okay?
So this is beer! It's bitter,
but there's more to it than that.
That's why it goes so great
with fried and salty food!
Okay, then...
So juicy!
Now take a slug of beer.
Right? Isn't that delicious?
They go fantastic together!
The beer resets the grease from the chicken
for fresh new flavor with every bite!
Wow, you really chugged it.
So what's your verdict?
It's great ! So you drink alcohol with food, huh?
Some people savor it on its own.
It doesn't matter as long
as you're enjoying yourself.
In that case, as you so kindly suggested,
I'm gonna do just that!
That's right--go on, now!
Hey! Just how much are you ordering?!
Your wallet is already dead.
Shut up! Cancel! Cancel those!
Hidebu!
Pardon me...
No horsing around, please.
I'm sorry.
Sheesh. Quit screwing around or--
Yow ! Spicy!
"Russian Roulette Octopus Balls"
"Only 1 is Super Spicy!"
"8 for ¥550"
What is this?
Looks like one of them is ultra spicy.
Beer! Beer!
It's empty?!
And no water, either!
Uzaki, a drink! Anything!
Wait just a sec, okay? I'm looking.
I can't wait!
Oh, I bet I can make this one.
I should make it for you sometime!
I'm begging you: make it snappy!
I thought I was a goner...
Hey, this is good!
I think I might like yuzu liqueur.
Good for you.
Another round!
Now wait just one minute!
What's up?
You're really knocking 'em back there.
Take it easy--it is your first time.
Pardon me!
Your yuzu liqueur.
Much obliged!
That's too fast !
But I'm totally fine.
Fine? How many is that?
Good question.
Is it, now?
Well, whatever.
Drink some water in there, too.
I just might be a heavyweight!
Look, just slow down, will you?
Sorry for the wait! Your yuzu liqueur.
Thanks.
Yesss!
Thank you very much!
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
You okay there, Senpai? You're kinda wobbly!
You're the only one wobbling around here.
She started out okay but
turned out pretty much as I'd expected.
I jotted down how much you drank.
Stay under that amount next time, okay?
Wow, Senpai, you sure got tall all of a sudden.
That's a utility pole! Walk properly, will you?
Aw, c'mon, Senpai, carry me!
Let go of me!
Piggyback! Baby back... ribs...
Stop that! Your various...
areas... are all up on me!
Various areas? Whazzat mean?
What's touchin' where?
Jeez, she is one irritating drunk!
Smooshy...
Markin' you with my scent...
No way can I send her home on her own like this.
Here, stand up. I'll take you home.
Aw! I'm not goin' home!
Let's drink at your place, Senpai!
What, more drinking?!
Go home and get to sleep, dummy!
And stand up already! I can see your underwear!
Who're you callin' a dummy, huh?
Say, Senpai, d'you know what time it is?
Huh?
Yikes! That late?!
Oh, too bad! No more trains! Ha ha! You dummy!
You're the dummy who can't get home, dummy.
We can call a cab.
Uzaki's dumbass drinking drained me dry!
The ATM should still be running.
Ugh, but that access fee... and taxis
will be charging pricey late-night fares...
Let her stay over? I could never!
I can't think straight with this booze in me!
Quite the dilemma!
You wouldn't abandon your junior,
stuck away from home, would you?
Don't tell me this was
all calculated from the get-go!
I don't even care anymore.
We're going to the convenience store.
I want some water.
Yeah! And alcohol!
I wanna verify my age! 'Cause I'm 20!
Whatever you want.
Look, just so you know,
I only have one futon set.
Wanna sleep together?
I'm splitting it up, moron! One quilt each!
Senpai... Hey, Senpai...
Don't go to sleep, huh?
I'm begging you, let me sleep.
It's three in the morning!
Let's play a game.
No way. You play dirty.
Aw...
Are you still drinking?!
Yep!
Honestly... She needs to learn
about the horrors of alcohol.
Squid's yummy...
No--come morning, she'll know.
Uh-oh... I really am sleepy.
Fine. I'll just sleep right here, then.
All right!
No stun-locking moves this time,
so let's get sparrin'!
Senpai? Hey, Senpai!
Pipe down.
Senpai? Are you asleep for real?
Well, well.
Leaving behind your junior
and just... going to sleep?
Just ignore her.
Maybe he'll wake up if I kiss him.
See, I knew you were only faking!
Don't get so worked up.
It was just a joke--a joke!
But you sure were frantic there, Senpai.
Have you never been kissed, by any chance?
No! Shut up! Go to sleep, idiot!
Sleepytime...
Aw...
My head hurts... I feel awful...
That's called a hangover.
Life's going to suck for a while.
I hate it!
Why are you just fine?
Grown-ups drink in moderation
so that doesn't happen.
What's "modera"--
Don't worry. Everyone has an alcohol screw-up.
Good thing your first time wasn't
at some sketchy drinking party.
It's not good at all!
But you found your limit right off the bat.
He's in lecture mode.
You didn't drink much water, either.
It takes water to metabolize alcohol.
Alternate with drinks of water
and you won't get sick.
You should feel better by noon.
Just have to tough it out.
Are you listening?
Wow, she's in hell.
The bigger the screw-up, the better the lesson.
Next time, drink as much water as you do booze.
'S fine. I won't drink again as long as I live.
Probably for the best.
Though everyone with a hangover says that.
Never... ever again.
I'm going to hit the store--
you hold down the fort.
Rest up, okay?
Senpai?
Yeah?
Thanks a lot... for being with me... at the pub.
It was fun.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
Oh, I nearly forgot: You're 20 now, Uzaki--
Happy birthday.
Something's happening!
Hmm.
Sak!