Slow jazz at a moderate volume,
not-too-bright lighting,
and the soothing aroma of brewing coffee.
It has been my business policy
from the very day we opened up shop
to provide a place where
customers can feel at ease.
Sakurai, a customer's getting ready to pay his check.
Would you mind?
Wow.
You picked up on that so quickly.
Mhm. Once you've got a decade of experience
under your belt, you'll start seeing it, too.
Sakurai started working for us
last year, and he's pretty good.
Have a nice day.
He may have a bit of a scary face,
but he makes up for it with his attentiveness.
He understands my business policy,
and whatever may happen,
he handles it with poise.
He never makes a fuss, or—
Sakurai!
I've never heard Sakurai screech like that.
So this is where you work!
It's super close to school, huh?
Niiice!
A close friend, perhaps?
Why didn't you tell me?
I was just on my way back
from a friend's place nearby,
then I got hungry and figured I'd go grab a bite!
Go home!
Why?!
Or perhaps an enemy.
This may be where I work part-time,
but it's also a safe haven for me to relax. So leave!
Hey, what gives?
Let me relax, too!
I'm starving!
Then go eat somewhere that isn't here.
Wow, sure are cold, aren't we?
What's the deal?
Let me order here!
You clash with the vibe here.
Huh? Excuse me?
That's awful! This is discrimination!
No wonder you're such a loner.
That's got fuck-all to do with it!
Mhm... I appear to have missed
my window for standing up.
Oh! Are you the owner?
My name's Hana Uzaki!
Thanks for taking care of Sakurai{*Senpai)!
Who do you think you are, my mother?
Whatcha up to?
Oh, uh, just checking our stock.
I see... So he's your senior.
Then you're in elem—er, middle school?
I'm a college student!
We go to the same college.
She's a year below me.
Also, I could totally hear you
say "elementary school", y'know?!
Can't really blame him, right, shorty?
Oh, shut it and keep it shut!
I... I was wrong?
It looks like he's in shock.
This is unlike him, though.
All these years I've spent in the café business,
refining my eye for people...
and I was wrong?!
Oh!
In college, you said?
So that means you're an adult.
Huh? Yeah, that's right. I'm an adult.
My impression of the owner sure changed
drastically over these last few minutes.
I'm sure this booth'll do.
Go on, take a seat.
Your order?
Hey, Sakurai, what's with the attitude here?
Huh?
I'm your customer right now.
Cus. To. Mer.
Seeing this makes me question
your behaviour towards other customers.
Need me to get a dictionary and
look up "customer service" for you?
"Customer service"?
For who? You?
'Scuse me, sir!
This employee has a bad attitude!
You oughta give him a pay cut!
Shut up!
If you ain't gonna order, beat it!
These youngsters sure are funny.
I think I'll watch them for a bit.
You've gotta take your job seriously
no matter the customer.
That's what being a pro's all about!
Sure, but if I did take it seriously,
you'd just make fun of me!
No way I would!
To be honest, it's embarrassing
when people I know see me working.
But it's so close to campus.
Haven't any of your other friends eaten here?
Did you treat them this poorly, too?
Oh!
Oh, you silly.
You're the only one I treat like this.
You're special.
Got it? Then have a soda or
something and get lost, dumdum.
Hearing you hurl that abuse with
such a straight face seriously pisses me off!
Now, now, Sakurai.
Go show her how you usually do things.
He's always so great with customers.
Yes, sir.
That's the spirit!
I'd like to order one serving
of excellent customer service!
Now start over, beginning with a glass of water!
You seriously get on my nerves, y'know that?
May I have your order, please?
Nope! Nuh-uh! No can do!
What happened to that glare of yours?
You lose it somewhere?
You're overreacting, Sakurai!
You know how easy it is to laugh
when you're not supposed to!
Ugh! I knew this would happen, dammit!
I'm sorry! I'll stop!
Please give me something to eat!
Can it!
You're free to go for today, Sakurai.
I-It's getting dark. Walk her home.
You're laughing too, boss?
You're doing an awful job hiding it!
Cya tomorrow.
I'm positively starving.
Let's stop somewhere!
Go straight home and eat there.
Aw!
Then at least let me order
something at the café next time.
Sure, no prob.
Stop by when I'm not working next time.
What?!
I promise I won't laugh next time!
Even when I see your smile—
Why, you...!
It's a nice café, though.
Yeah.
Quiet, just stylish enough...
Uh-huh.
It really is a nice place.
I dig the atmosphere there.
Oh, I know!
Maybe I should get a part-time job there, too!
You know, with you!
Sure.
Wouldn't that be a blast?
Mhm-hmm.
Don't you dare.
Why?!
Why do I crack open brand-new
games in the middle of the night?
A little Sakurai-teasing
will get me through the day!
Huh?
Ow! Ow, ow!
Whoa! I just wanted to pet you...
Aren't you energetic, you little—
Ow! Hey, that hurts!
C'mon, now—
Ew.
What are you doing so early
in the morning, Sakurai?
It's creepy.
Oh, Uzaki.
I found this stray.
It isn't running away,
so I figured I could pet it.
Huh! Must be used to people.
It won't let me pet it, though.
It just keeps clawing away at me.
You sure seem happy despite that.
I mean... it's cute.
Ew.
Be that as it may, you're obviously
no expert at handling animals.
Uh, yeah...
Put your hand below eye level.
Cats get scared when bigger beasties
reach down over their heads.
Makes sense, yeah.
Instead, bring it in from below and be patient.
There you go. Good kitty. Good kitty.
Whoa!
See? It's easy when they're used to people.
Nice...
It might belong to a family in the neighbourhood,
or maybe someone's just feeding it.
You sure know a lot about cats.
We have cats at home.
Two of them!
Wow, really?
Want to stop by some time to meet them?
I'd love to give those cats a good rubbing,
but a guy going to a girl's house alone?
Oh!
It ran away.
The sound of those brakes must've spooked it.
Cats hate high-pitched noises.
It probably lives around here.
You're sure to see it again.
Okay, Sakurai, let's get to class!
Whoa!
I wanted to pet it... just once...
Sure got to you, huh?
Nah. I'm fine.
I love cats and dogs,
but pets aren't allowed at my or my parent's homes.
I've rarely had the opportunity to pet a cat.
Then I'm gonna go catch that one!
Huh?
It can't have gone far, and it's so
tame around humans that it might just work!
You don't have to! Stop!
If I strike out, we'll visit
a cat café one of these days!
Really?!
There you are!
Hi-yah!
Wait for me, kitty cat!
What happened?!
Sakurai! Bad news! S.O.S.!
What's up?
Huh?!
Hey!
I'm stuck...
Put that ass away!
Yeowch!
What's the big idea?!
S-Sorry! I-It just... slipped out...
So why hit me?
Well, I could see your pa... pan... underwear.
I was trying to fix your skirt.
What?!
W-Well... okay.
He saw my undies? Wait—he touched my butt!
Whatever. We'll have a nice, long chat about it later.
Look, could you pull me out from behind?
Grab my waist.
G-Got it.
Wow, her waist is so slim...
Whoa! Stop! Stop!
Huh?
Uh-oh. My clothes are caught!
If this goes on, I'll end up flashing my boobs!
D-Don't say "boobs"!
First, somehow get my shirt untangled,
then pull a little at a time so nothing tears!
I'm counting on you! It's brand new!
Geez, you're so demanding!
Are you pulling out, Sakurai? Hurry!
Almost there, so just behave, will—
Eh? Huh? Whoa!
You've got the wrong idea!
Aren't you done yet?
Man, I had no clue what was
gonna happen for a bit there!
Thanksies, Sakurai!
We can forget about that whole butt thing.
C'mon, let's get to class!
I just wanna go home.
Then how's a cat café sound?
Maybe next time.
Eating in the dining hall today, Sakurai?
Uzaki...
Hmm? What's up?
It's kinda hard to look her in the eye
after what happened earlier.
Aha!
Are you embarrassed to be eating alone?
What?
Unfortunately, I'm already eating with
another friend of mine, so you're on your own.
I know you're lonely, but please,
hold back your tears.
Oh, shut up! I'm eating with a friend!
Eh? Huh?!
What's up? You're spilling that like crazy, y'know?
You've got friends?!
That is outstandingly rude!
Oh, man! What now?!
I'd better say hi to your friend, huh?
Who are you, my mother?
Beat it!
Moron.
Huh?
What's that numbskull doing?
What you looking at, huh?
Seriously, what's that numbskull's deal?
I just don't get it.
And what's up with her unfounded concern?
Your noodles are getting soggy, Hana.
You shouldn't be staring at
your phone while eating.
Uh-huh.
Thank you very much.
Please come again.
How about a drink once you're
done tidying up, Sakurai?
Oh, thank you!
I'd appreciate it.
You're about halfway through college life, eh?
How are you doing on credits?
They're... coming along.
My daughter took all kinds of courses.
Now she just dawdles around every day.
It's better that way.
I'm jealous!
Well, it's definitely preferable over
regretting it later down the road.
This place really is an oasis.
Slow jazz at a moderate volume,
and the soothing aroma of brewing coffee.
It feels like time flows differently here.
It truly lets you feel at ease.
Sakurai!
Hi!
Not you again!
I told you to stay away while I'm here!
Aw, don't be so cold!
Besides, what's the point if you're not here?
I couldn't wait any longer to see you!
Uh... I... what? What are you talking about?!
I have to resubmit my essay!
Please help a girl out!
Huh?
Oh... an essay, huh?
You always were good at writing them...
No can do.
What? Why?!
Can't you tell that I'm on the clock?
I'll wait!
Use that time to do it yourself!
I don't think I can do it on my own!
How'd you make it all the way to college?
C'mon, please help me out!
Look here, you...
Now, now, Sakurai.
Your junior is counting on you.
Why, ain't that adorable?
We're closing up for the night. Feel free to
stick around and work on that essay.
Huh?
Really?!
We don't have any customers right now.
It's fun watching the banter between these two.
A little something for my best
junior employee. It's on the house.
There's really no need for that.
Hooray! You're so generous, sir!
Essay first, food after.
Wow. Strict.
You're almost at the finish line!
This part needs fixing up.
"I think" is something a grade-schooler would write.
Change it to "It's thought" or "It's considered".
You're in college. Leave childish sentences behind.
Now me, I'd boost the word count with
"In the author's opinion, it would appear that..."
I see...
Once that's rectified,
all that's left is the closing sentence.
Write that and be done with it.
Oh, right! I've been meaning
to ask you something.
Can't concentrate to save your life, can you?
Can I swing by your place?
Absolutely not.
No hesitation whatsoever.
Where'd that come from, anyway?
I just wanna check it out!
"Just" my ass!
I'm not "just" gonna let you upend
my lifestyle for your entertainment.
I won't upend anything! So why can't I?
Why?! I mean...
She's gotta be kidding, right?
I have no reason to let you into my place.
Sure you do. You said you live alone, right?
You can save money if I cook,
and your place is closer to campus.
See? There are way more pros than cons!
You've gotta be kidding, right?
Is your cooking even edible?
Now, that's just rude! It totally is!
If you say so.
Now, back to that essay.
Hold on, what was the last pro there?
Huh?
My place is close to campus and...?
Well, since it's so close,
I figure I could sleep in—
You're not spending the night!
Th-That's... unbelievable!
What are you angry about?
Look, I-I'm not angry.
It's just that you...
What's up?
Letting you in my apartment is one thing...
It's... not so simple for a girl...
to to sleep in a guy's room...
You don't want me to?
Wh... What?!
We can play versus and co-op all night long!
Eh?
You can't hide it from me, Sakurai!
I know you bought that new game!
You're on my friend list!
If we stop by after class, we can
hang out and play any day of the week!
Y-You bumbling idiot! Dumbass! Utter imbecile!
Why?!
You asshat!
I opened this café for the thrill of
getting a glimpse into all kinds of lives.
I can't believe you!
What makes me an idiot?!
You just are!
But these two are the best.
I could watch them forever.
Takes one to know one, dontcha think?
Nah, you're just an absolute twit!
If Sakurai quit, the show would be over.
For crying out loud, stop calling me dumb!
Maybe I should give him a raise.
Guess we'll see Ami next time.