Sakurai, we'll be on a family trip
to the hot springs during Golden Week.
You'll have that time off.
Why not go on holiday somewhere?
Maybe...
So she suggested, but...
I've been non-stop gaming
for about seventy-two hours since.
Oh, that's the last one?
Let's do this.
That obnoxious rhythmic flourish...
Howdy, Sakurai!
It had to be you.
Are you free today? You gotta be, right?
Don't drop by unannounced
with all that rubbish.
Figured I should, since loners like you
always hole up and game when they're off work.
And wow, turns out I was right!
I'm speechless.
So here I am, ready to hang out with
Mr. Games-Are-My-Only-Friends!
Great news, ye?
Drop the condescending tone. It pisses me off.
And so...
Wanna go play Doramon GO™ on the go?
I'd still be gaming!
There's a big spawning event during Golden Week.
Let's catch 'em all—together!
Well, I do have the app, but...
Buuuuut?
But playing alone is too embarrassing, so I didn't.
You got that right!
Man, I can read you like a book!
Why'd you turn it off?!
C'mon, let's play together!
Talk about a major pain in the behind.
Though we do have a long holiday...
C'mon, Sakurai...
I'm dying of boredom anyway, so sure. I'm in.
Hooray!
I found a Lousy Cat!
Check this out, Sakurai!
Huh?
If looks could kill, you'd be a murderer.
Gamed too much.
Being all scowly's one thing,
but walking around with that face?
Someone's gonna report you.
Mind not slowly backing away like that?
Christ.
But hey, you sure seem to be catching a lot!
A lotta gorillas, that is.
It's just one after another.
Ugh, my eyes sting. Screen's too bright.
Oh! How's going glasses shopping sound?
Welcome.
Huh? Ami, that you?
Oh, my!
Fancy running into you two!
I see. So your eyes hurt
from playing games too much.
If this keeps up, he'll be Doramon GO™-ing
straight to the police station!
You wanna have a Doramon GO™ at it?
Sakurai, you've done nothing but play video games
while we were at the hot springs?
Sorry.
And I bet he'd still be going at it
if I didn't come knocking!
No denying that.
Hey, I know!
Since she's here anyway, why not
get Ami to be your glassistant?
My glassistant?
Is there something you're looking for?
Yeah, this hermit of a gamer here
is in dire need of a specific item:
Computer glasses!
Oh, the ones that cut down
on blue light from LCDs?
These bad boys are supposed to
keep your eyes from getting strained!
I've always wanted a pair myself!
Mhm. Might be good for long gaming sessions.
Huh! The lenses are a faint yellow.
So they're like thin sunglasses, eh?
You're really rocking those glasses!
Yes! It's perfect!
Eh?
Can you try these on real quick?
Mhm?
Oh, nice! Should we try on some others?
Totes!
Ooh, which ones?
How about these?
Like I'm some kind of dress-up doll.
Those are perfect!
R-Really?
Yup! It hides your glare so well that
you almost look normal!
Hides what glare, exactly?!
Wouldn't it be best if you wore those
in school and at work, too?
Oh, shut it.
Then how about these?
Where'd you find those?
Et tu, Ami? Why join in on this mockery?
Oh, wow. This is priceless. Can I take a pic?
No way in hell!
Lookie here... or on second thought, please don't.
I can't stop laughing. It's hard to aim!
Knock it off!
Dammit...
Try, uh, these on next, Sakurai!
You're already in tears!
With your natural fierce look,
you look like a real mafioso!
Like someone who'd assassinate
people with a fibre wire!
Or like the mob boss of the criminal underworld!
Oh!
Throw on a white coat and
you'd nail the mad scientist look!
Wanna try it?
Hell, no!
What shelf were these on?
I'm putting them back!
Sakurai, please! Just once!
Brush your hair back with
those little round glasses on!
Just once, I swear!
You'll turn into an
embarrassingly tropey character!
What are you expecting from me?!
Sorry, sorry! This is the last pair.
Seriously this time.
Pretty please?
Uh... sure.
Now make a fist.
Raise your arm.
Open your mouth a little.
Ayyyyy-oh!
Oh, man, that was the best!
You should go pick out glasses for yourself, Hana.
Good point!
What'll it be?
Gee, which ones?
These might suit you, don't you think?
I do dig a pink frame...
But red is rad!
Ooh, yeah!
Check it out, Sakurai.
Doesn't Hana look good in glasses?
Whaddya think?
Strangely enough, they make you
look even dumber.
"Strangely enough"?!
Hey, I was complimenting you earlier!
Then you called me a mafioso!
That makes it a wash, you dolt!
Picky, picky!
That's what you are, you know that?
You get what's coming for you
when you act like that!
Well, it's always you who's
getting angry at everything!
Oh, shut it! You always ask for it, dumbass!
Only a dumbass calls others dumbasses, dumbass!
So you'd be a dumbass too then, right, dumbass?
Dumbass!
Doesn't count if you said it first,
dumbass! Dumbass! Dumbass!
Is it fine to leave them like that?
Yup. They always act like this.
Boooo, I missed out on getting
glasses thanks to you.
Ooh! Caught me a Lousy Cat Dandy!
You just had to start trouble.
Another Gorilla.
C'mon, be the bigger man and
learn to take some responsibility.
That's power harassment.
Ey, got a Lousy Cat Genius this time!
It's obviously the fault of whoever
started it, which would be you.
Nothing but Gorillas.
See, your problem is—
Thanks.
Uh... Don't mention it.
The next station is: Nechst Station.
Lotta people getting on now.
But with this game, the monster spawn rates
increase when there's more people.
See? A Lousy Cat Cyborg!
Still nothing but bloody Gorillas here.
Just how much into gorillas are ya?
Not one bit. They're into me.
Well, so long as we reach our destination.
The next station is: Andenechst Station.
The next station is: Andefallo-Wing Station.
Now it's crazy crowded.
Oh, right. There's a football match
at a nearby stadium.
Explains.
Pardon me, ook-ook.
S-Something incredibly soft is...
I-I'm sorry.
It's fine. Not much we can do about it.
This is hell. And it'll only get worse at this rate!
I can't budge!
Am I just gonna have to grin and bear it?
Calm down. Get a grip, dude!
Think of something else and try to calm down!
S-Sakurai?
I-It's nothing.
Why are those ads there of all places?!
Gotta get my mind on something else, pronto...
Sakurai?
I'm fine. I'm totally fine.
There's nothing but traps,
no matter where I look!
I see nothing. I hear nothing.
I turn my consciousness inward.
What's wrong with him?
He got so quiet all of a sudden.
Oh, his eyelashes are really long.
Wai—his face is so close!
Picture it—now! A clear blue sky!
This is like one of those
wall-slam things, huh? Ha, ha...
Ah, Bliss, stretching far and vast!
Isn't your arm getting tired? Don't overdo it.
Crystal-clear, unclouded water,
its surface like a mirror!
Earth to Sakurai...
I can do this. I can make it if I keep this up!
With my eyes closed and my ears dulled,
my other senses are heighten—
Hey, uh, Sakurai... Thanks for earli—
Eh?
Sakurai!
Is he out cold—on his feet?
Step back; doors closing.
Hey! This is our stop!
Sakurai? Sakurai!
N-Now what?
Where am I?
What time is it even?
Oh.
I got a ton of calls from Uzaki.
And... one of these.
So that's what happened...
...during Golden Week?
Yes.
I shouldn't laugh.
And?
And nothing.
I blacked out before it got to that point.
What?
If she made me feel that way,
I figured I'd be better off unconscious!
I see.
Wait, can he just flip his
consciousness on and off at will?
What is he, a ninja? Spooky.
Well, don't fret over it too much.
You're still young. You ought to be more carefree.
I mean, look at Ami. She hangs out
with the boys a lot as well.
With boys? Me?
Not at all.
See? Not at all!
Not at all? Seriously?
Yes, seriously.
Wha—?!
I'm sorry.
What for?
Huh!
But that happening right after
sounds hilar—er, terrible!
I heard that Freudian slip!
That was unfortunate.
Yeah, well.
Make sure you follow up with Hana.
She's the one who invited you along, after all.
Yeah... I guess you're right.
I don't know what's going on, but I'm
not engaging. Looks like a pain in the ass.
Listen to this, Sakurai.
She's engaging me.
Did something nice happen?
I was looking at the calendar when it hit me.
Right.
There are no holidays in June.
And that's why you're so down?!
You've still got weekends off.
But the longer and more numerous
the breaks, the better, dontcha think?
Greedy much?
A three-day break really winds you up!
Besides, I get depressed thinking about
this weather sticking around for another month.
Sure. But after the rainy
season comes summer break.
But not before exams.
I wanna go have fun!
Let's do that, then.
How's next weekend sound?
You're serious?!
Don't startle me!
That's my line!
This same old loner of a senior,
suggesting we go somewhere?
Hell must be frozen over!
Now I know where the rain's coming from!
It's because you say such weird stuff! Ugh!
Calm your horses!
I can't make heads or tails
of this mixed-up conversation!
But well, if it doesn't work out for you, forget it.
I'll go!
Well... glad to hear that.
So, is there someplace you had in mind?
I know! How about an outing by train?
Sakurai, your face is all red.
It's nothing. Trains are banned.
Then do you mind if I just
throw something together?
Not at all, be my guest.
Got it! I can't wait!
That's one frightening laugh.
Still, it's not every day that you invite me!
Well, yeah. I felt bad for
what happened over Golden Week.
Sakurai...
And when I told Ami,
she said I should follow up with you.
Huh? You upset?
Am not.
Pull the other one.
For real.
Oh, c'mon. Be real.
Look, if I were mad, it'd be a big deal!
The hell's that supposed to mean?
It's pouring. Forget going out in this.
I hope she's still home...
I was literally just about to call you.
I figured it'd still be pissing down today,
so I thought we'd just play games at your place.
"Might as well cook, too!" I thought,
but then it came down even harder...
By the time I exited the supermarket,
it was hell out there.
I appreciate the sentiment,
but don't go overboard.
Can I borrow your shower?
Oh, and a change of clothes.
Aw, shouldn't have worn my favourite shirt.
Care to join me?
Get in already, you imp!
Honestly.
Whoa! I'm soaked clear through to my undies!
Too much info!
This shirt is ginormous!
Lemme get lunch done before we play.
Hey, uh, thanks.
Ta-dah!
You don't have any good cookware,
so I'm giving you my old pot.
That's incredibly nice of you. I appreciate it.
First...
Need a hand?
You're no cook.
How about you wash these veggies?
Yeah, sure.
You're awfully obedient today, Sakurai.
It's just that everything's been
going wrong for you today, so...
No worries, I'm a bona fide chef!
You said you couldn't taste the porridge
I made for you when you were sick,
so there's a little score-settling in the mix.
I'm really sorry I said that.
My cooking will have your
unsophisticated palate moaning!
Taking it one step too far, again.
What game did you have in mind?
Oh! You downloaded Meowcraft! Let's play that!
Let's work together to build
something totally out-there!
This is too perfect a way for
a college student to waste a day off.
Ah, who cares?
Ready to start being
a useless college student?
What do you mean, "start"?
You've always been one.
Back off!
Now that's what I'd call a LAN party.
Guess I was overzealous, thinking we
could finish building that in one day.
It did get torn down a few times.
We can just work on it further
the next time you're over.
The... next time?
Hmm?
Yeah!
Enough with that scary laugh!
Put the curry pot in
the fridge just like that, 'kay?
Will do.
It'll taste even better after sitting overnight.
You know, I've heard that before. Is it true?
Let it sit overnight and the roux
soaks into the meat and veggies,
which release their umami components,
amino acids, sugars, into the roux!
That's how you get a richer
umami flavour all throughout the curry.
Too long; didn't listen.
I'm looking forward to it.
Good!
Though today's portion was plenty good already.
Sakurai?
About that next time...
Would tomorrow work?
Oh, to pick up where we left off?
Sure. Got all the time in the world.
Hooray!
Then let's hang out again, okay?
Yep.
Um... wait—what?
Sorry. I seem to have
left my pass at your place.
You're so disorganised.