Sakurai, we'll be on a family trip
to the hot springs during Golden Week.
You'll have that time off.
Why not go on holiday somewhere while you're free?
Maybe...
That's what she suggested, but...
I've been nonstop gaming
for about seventy-two hours since.
Oh, that's the last one?
Let's do this.
That unnecessary rhythmic flourish...
Howdy, Sakurai!
I knew it.
Are you free today?
I mean, you totally are, right?
Don't just pop in unannounced and spout rubbish.
Well, I figured I'd drop by since loners like you
always hole up playing games when they're off work.
And wow, turns out I was right!
I have no words.
So here I am to hang out with you,
my senior but above all else, friend!
Great news, ye?
Drop the condescending tone, it pisses me off.
And so...
Wanna play Doramon GO™ on the go?
That's still a game!
There's a big spawning event during Golden Week.
Let's catch 'em all—together!
I have it, too.
Buuut?
But playing alone is too embarrassing, so I didn't.
Sure is! Man, I can read you like a book!
Why'd you turn it off?!
C'mon, let's play together!
Talk about a major pain in the behind,
Though we do have holiday...
C'mon, Sakurai...
I'm about to die of boredom, so sure, I'll play along.
Hooray!
I found a Lousy Cat!
Check this out, Sakurai!
Huh?
If looks could kill,
yours would be the most lethal.
Gamed too much.
Being all scowly's one thing, but walking around
with that face on top of that?
Someone's gonna report you.
Mind not slowly backing away like that?
Christ.
But hey, you sure seem to be catching a lot!
A lotta gorillas, that is.
It's just one after another.
Ugh, my eyes sting. Screen's too bright.
Oh! How's going glasses shopping sound?
Welcome.
Huh? Ami, that you?
Oh, my!
Fancy running into you two!
I see. So your eyes hurt
from playing games too much.
If this keeps up, he'll be Doramon GO™-ing
straight to the police station!
You wanna have a Doramon GO™ at it?
Sakurai, you've done nothing but play video games
while we were at the hot springs?
Sorry.
And I bet he'd still be going at it
if I didn't come knocking!
No denying that.
Hey, I know!
Since she's here anyway, why not
get Ami to be your glassistant?
My glassistant?
Is there something you're looking for?
Yeah, this hermit gaming-addict here
is in dire need of a specific item:
Computer glasses!
Oh, the ones that cut down
on blue light from LCD displays?
These bad boys are supposed to
keep your eyes from getting strained!
I've always wanted a pair myself!
Mhm. Might be good for long gaming sessions.
Huh! The lenses are a faint yellow.
So they're like thin sunglasses, eh?
You really rock the glasses look!
Yes! It's perfect!
Eh?
Can you try these on real quick?
Mhm?
Oh, nice! Should we try on some others?
Totes!
Ooh, which ones?
How about these?
Like I'm some kind of dress-up doll.
Those are perfect!
R-Really?
Yup! It hides your glare so well that
you almost look normal!
Who said I don't look normal?!
You should probably wear
those at work and school, too!
Oh, shut it.
Then how about these?
Where'd you find those?
Et tu, Ami? Why join in making fun of me?
Oh, wow. This is priceless. Can I take a pic?
Absolutely not!
Lookie here... or y'know what, don't.
I can't stop laughing. It's hard to aim!
Knock it off!
Dammit...
Try, uh, these on next, Sakurai!
You're already in tears!
Combined with your natural fierce look,
you get the ultimate mafioso look!
Like you'd assassinate somebody with a fibre wire!
Or like you were dominating the criminal underworld!
Oh!
Throw on a white coat and
you'd nail the mad scientist look!
Wanna try?
No, thanks!
What shelf were these on?
I'm putting them back!
Sakurai, please! Just once!
Brush your hair back with
those little round glasses on!
Just once, I swear!
You'll turn into an
embarrassingly tropey character!
What is it you want from me?
Sorry, sorry! This is the final pair.
These were a serious choice.
Okay?
Uh... okay.
Now make a fist.
Raise your arm.
Open your mouth a little.
Ayyyyy-oh!
Oh, man, that was the best!
You'd better pick out
your own glasses there, Hana.
Hey, right!
What'll it be?
Gee, which ones?
These might suit you, don't you think?
I do dig a pink frame...
But red is rad!
Ooh, yeah!
Check it out, Sakurai.
Doesn't Hana look good in glasses?
Whaddya think?
You look dumber, strangely enough.
"Strangely enough"?!
Hey, I was complimenting you earlier!
Then you called me a mafioso!
That makes it a wash, you dolt!
Picky, picky!
That's what you are, you know that?
If anyone's gotta know what they are, it'd be you!
Well, it's always you who's
getting angry at everything!
Shut up! You asked for it, dumbass!
Only a dumbass calls others dumbasses, dumbass!
So you'd be a dumbass too then, right, dumbass?
Dumbass!
Doesn't count if you said it first,
dumbass! Dumbass! Dumbass!
Is this okay?
Uh-huh. They're always like that.
I missed out on getting glasses,
and it's all your fault.
Ooh! Got a Lousy Cat Dandy!
You just had to start something.
Another Gorilla.
Don't dump the blame on me
just 'cause you're older.
That's power harassment.
Hey, I got a Lousy Cat Genius this time!
Clearly it's your fault, because you started it.
Nothing but Gorillas.
See, your problem is—
Thanks.
Uh... yeah.
Nechst Station. Nechst Station.
Lot of people getting on.
But with this game, the more people
around you, the higher the monster spawn rate.
See? A Lousy Cat Cyborg!
Still Gorillas here.
Just how much do you like gorillas?
I don't. They like me.
Well, as long as we get where we're going.
Andenechst Station.
Andefallo-Wing Station.
Now it's crazy crowded.
Oh, right—there's a soccer match
at a nearby stadium.
That explains it.
Pardon me, huh-huh.
S-Something incredibly soft...
I-I'm sorry.
It's okay. Can't really help it in all this.
This is bad—and at this rate,
it'll get really bad!
I can't budge!
Am I just going to have to grin and bear it?
Calm down. Get a hold of yourself!
Think of something else
and pull yourself together!
S-Sakurai?
It's n-nothing.
What's that doing here?!
Gotta get my mind on something else, pronto...
Sakurai?
I am fine. I'm fine.
There are traps everywhere I turn!
I see nothing. I hear nothing.
I turn my consciousness inward.
What's wrong with him?
He got so quiet all of a sudden.
Oh—his eyelashes are really long.
His face is so close!
Picture it—now! A clear blue sky!
This is like one of those
wall-pound things, huh? Ha ha...
A vast field, stretching
as far as the eye can see!
Isn't your arm tired? Don't overdo it.
Crystal-clear, unclouded water,
its surface like a mirror!
Say something...
I can do this. I can make it through!
With my eyes closed and my ears dulled,
my other senses are heighten—
Hey, uh, Sakurai... Thanks for earli—
Eh?
Sakurai!
Is he out cold—on his feet?
The door is closing.
Hey! This is our stop!
Sakurai? Sakurai!
Now... Now what?
Where am I?
Wait—what time is it?
Oh.
I got a ton of calls from Uzaki.
And... one of these.
So that's what happened during...
...during Golden Week?
Yes.
No laughing.
And?
And nothing.
I blacked out before it got to that point.
What?
If she made me feel that way,
I figured I'd be better off unconscious!
I see.
Wait, can he just turn his
consciousness off and on at will?
What is he, a ninja? Spooky.
Well, don't worry too much about it.
You're young—you should be more carefree.
I mean, I'm sure my Ami
is hanging out with boys.
With boys?
No, not at all.
See? Not at all!
Not at all? Really?
Yes, really.
What?!
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Huh!
To think something so hilar—er,
terrible happened to you afterward!
You were going to say "hilarious"!
That was unfortunate.
Yeah, well.
Follow up with Hana.
After all, she's the one who invited you along.
Yeah... I guess you're right.
I don't know what's going on,
but I'm not going to engage. Too much trouble.
Listen to this, Sakurai.
She's engaging me.
Did something happen?
I was looking at the calendar when it hit me.
Yeah?
There are no holidays in June.
And that's why you're so down?!
You've still got weekends off.
But the more and longer breaks
the better, don't you think?
Greedy much?
A three-day break really winds you up!
Besides, I get depressed thinking
about this weather sticking around
for another month.
Sure. But after the rainy
season comes summer break.
But not before exams.
I wanna go have fun!
Let's do that, then.
How about next weekend?
You mean it?!
Don't startle me!
You startled me!
This same old loner of a senior,
suggesting we go somewhere?
Hell must be frozen over! Completely frozen over!
And now I know why it's raining!
Because you say such weird stuff! Ugh!
Calm down!
I can't make heads or tails
of this mixed-up conversation!
If it doesn't work for you, then never mind.
I'll go!
Well... good.
So... is there someplace you had in mind?
I know: How about an outing by train?
Sakurai, your face is all red.
It's nothing. No trains.
Then do you mind if I just
throw something together?
Please do.
Got it! I can't wait!
That's one frightening laugh.
Still, it's not every day that you invite me.
Yeah, well, I felt bad for what
happened over Golden Week.
Sakurai...
And when I told Ami,
she said I should follow up with you.
Huh? Are you mad?
I'm not mad.
You totally are.
Not in the slightest.
Oh, come on.
Look, if I were mad, it'd be a big deal!
What the hell?
It's pouring. Forget going out in this.
I hope she's still home...
I was just about to call you.
I figured if it was gonna rain anyway,
I may as well play games at your place.
I thought I'd cook, so I did a little shopping,
and it started raining harder...{I thought I'd cook while I have the chance..."
By the time I left the supermarket,
it was a total disaster.
I appreciate the sentiment,
but don't go overboard.
Can I borrow your shower?
Oh... and a change of clothes.
Aw, I shouldn't have worn my favorite shirt.
Care to join me?
Go already!
Honestly.
Whoa! I'm soaked clear through to my undies!
Ugh! TMI!
This shirt is ginormous!
I'll just get lunch started
before we start playing.
Hey, uh, thanks.
Ta-da!
You don't have any good cookware,
so I'm giving you my old pot.
That's incredibly nice of you. I appreciate it.
First...
Need help?
You're no cook. How about washing these veggies?
Yeah, sure.
You're awfully obedient today, Sakurai.
It's just that everything's been
going wrong for you today, so...
It's fine—I'm a good cook.
You said you couldn't taste the porridge
I made for you when you were sick,
so there's a little score-settling in the mix.
I'm really sorry I said that.
My cooking will have your
unsophisticated palate moaning!
Again, you've gone a step too far.
What game do you want to play?
Oh! You downloaded Meowcraft! Let's play that!
Let's work together to build
something totally out-there!
This is too perfect a way for
a college student to waste a day off.
Ah, whatever.
Ready to be a useless college student?
I mean, you've been one all along.
Back off!
Phew! That was fun!
I guess it was asking too much
to finish our build in one day.
It did get torn down a few times.
We can just work on it
the next time you're over.
The... next time?
Hmm?
Yeah!
Enough with the scary laugh!
Put the curry pot in
the fridge just like that, 'kay?
Will do.
It'll taste even better after sitting overnight.
You know, I've heard that. Is it true?
Let it sit overnight and the roux
soaks into the meat and veggies,
which release their umami components—amino
acids, sugars—into the roux!
That's how you get a richer
umami flavor all through the curry.
I'm sorry I asked.
I'm looking forward to it.
Good!
Though today's was already plenty good.
Sakurai?
You said "the next time"... How about tomorrow?
Oh, to pick up where we left off today?
Sure. God knows I'm free.
Hooray!
Then let's hang out again, okay?
Yep.
Um... wait—what?
Sorry. I seem to have
left my pass at your place.
You're so disorganized.
"Episode 5: I Want to Meddle
in My Friend's Business!"