Sakurai Shinichi started
working here part-time last year.
Though he looks a bit fierce,
he has a serious personality
and attitude toward work,
and our regulars say good things about him.
But most of all...
...his body is fine .
Whoops.
That Sakurai's something, all right.
On closer inspection, he's pretty hunky.
He looks slim, but he's got
proper muscles under there!
Sakurai? We're ready to pay.
Coming!
I doubt he's noticed, but he has plenty of fans.
Sakurai, you're so tall! How tall are you?
One hundred eighty centimeters.
Wow! That's tall, all right!
Did you play any sports?
I was in the swim club in high school.
Wow, really?
The swim team! Yes! Good question, ma'am!
And those swimmers...
why, you can see everything !
To be learning tidbit after tidbit,
right here at work...
I'm making such progress!
Your heart doesn't seem to be in it today, Ami.
Eh?
Getting lost in thought is fine and all,
but you are on the clock.
You've got to be careful in this line of work,
or you'll lose track of all kinds of things.
Right. I'm sorry.
I do understand your hobby, though.
Now go on--clear that open table.
Okay, Dad.
Dad may come across as gentle and tasteful,
but he sure is strict with family.
This won't do. Not when I'm actually
working the same shift as Sakurai!
Hiya!
You're here again?
Don't you have anything better to do?
I could ask you the same
thing--working on a Sunday!
Who's this? Who's this? Who ?
Hello there, Hana.
Dad knows her, too?
Sir! Up top! Yeah!
Yeah!
Dad... without a single shred of tastefulness!
Our peak time's just ended, so there
aren't many customers. Sit wherever you like.
Okay!
Um... who's that?
You mean Uzaki?
She's a sophomore at our college.
Ah! She's in college!
Oh, right, Senpai--I have that game you lent me.
Cool. How was it?
They're borrowing each other's stuff.
Must be good friends.
Whew, that final act was a real thrill.
Here I thought it was
an entirely different game,
but when I found out it was
kind of a sequel to the last one?
I got crazy goosebumps!
I know, right?
I would've been happy playing
a plain old building game,
but it turned out to be such a find,
I just had to get it out there!
What's this? They seem like such good friends.
No--they can't be--
Oh, those two?
What's with the chuckle?
Oh, nothing. Bring her some water, would you?
Welcome.
Thanks!
So, you go to the same college?
I'm Ami Asai. I'm a senior.
Oh, really? Then that makes you Senpai's senpai!
Be right back. I'm going to put this in my bag.
Sure.
I'm Hana Uzaki, and I'm a sophomore!
Now that I get a good look at her...
this girl is really cute !
Then there's her endearing smile...
She's short, so she has this
"adorable little animal" vibe.
She's no little animal. Holy... wowsers!
This girl is a beast !
Come on. Pull yourself together!
You and Sakurai seem to get along really well.
Hmm? Oh, yeah, we do!
How long have you known each other?
We were in the same club in high school.
The water on Uzaki's table
is getting pretty low.
He's always been a gloomy
Gus with an evil look in his eyes.
He was a hard person to get to know.
Even now, in college, his personality is
no better--he's always doing loner stuff.
So I'm looking out for him.
Ah! So that's how it is.
Huh?
Well, call me over
when you're ready to order, Hana.
'Kay!
Well?
She's just so good .
You want to stick your nose in their business...
But we shouldn't interfere...
Don't you just want to look out for them both?
I get that.
Don't you love customer-facing jobs?
You get to watch all kinds of people
and their lives--like those two.
It's one of the thrills of this business.
Uzaki. Water.
That's cold !
Wh-Where the heck did you come from?!
That's my line!
Customers are supposed to just
sit quietly! I was bringing it to you !
Seriously? You haven't even
been treating me like a customer!
Shut up!
They put on quite a show, am I right?
You're telling me.
I've got to start taking more shifts!
Oh, give them a towel.
What?!
Senpai's out with a cold?
Sakurai called this morning.
I made him take the day off.
First the ice-water drenching yesterday,
then it got so cold last night...
Well, huh. So much for that
"Oh, yeah--I train" expression.
He's surprisingly fragile.
Oh, yeah--I train.
Why doesn't she have a cold, then?
In that case, sir...
Man, I have been knocked flat .
Did colds always hit this hard?
Do I need a doctor? Medicine?
I should eat something first.
But I can't move.
Now what?
What a racket. Who's there? Dammit...
And me barely managing to get out of bed.
Hiya!
Do you really have a cold?
Well, I'm paying you a visit!
U-Uzaki?
What... how did you...
Are you okay, Senpai?!
Hey, uh... Senpai!
That must be one bad cold.
Yeah.
Well, I've let her into my place after all.
Who was it? Who told her where I live?
Oh? Was that wrong?
Since I know where he lives, I thought
we would play some games or something.
Now that's some misplaced excitement.
He looks like he's having a really bad time.
He brags about his stamina,
only to be laid up in bed. Fitting.
That does it.
Have you seen a doctor?
No... can't really move.
Any medicine?
Not yet. Haven't bought any.
Then you haven't eaten, either.
Oh, well. Leave this to me!
Uh...
Oof...
Going by his symptoms, I'd say this one.
A cold--that calls for leeks!
Can you sit up, Senpai?
Yeah.
Then eat--even if it's only a few bites.
Wow.
It was a real production, let me tell you!
Empty fridge, awkward kitchen...
Here you go. Say "ah"!
I-I can feed myself.
Stop that!
It's good.
Right?!
Honestly... I'm not tasting things
too well right now.
But... it's probably good.
"Probably," huh?
I'll take it.
Sorry.
See? My cooking is totally edible.
Eating really warmed me up.
You got a good sweat going on!
And now?
Strip!
I refuse.
No way! Wipe yourself down and change clothes!
That sweat? It stinks !
It's fine! I'm just going to
take my medicine and go to sleep!
Hey! Don't fight me, sickie!
You've got nice skin, mister. I'll be gentle!
No weird roleplay!
Forget feeling self-conscious, now!
You must be used to going
around half-naked from swim club.
I'll do the front myself!
How can being cared for be so tiring?
Here's your medicine. Take this
and you'll be all better in the morning.
But if you're still feeling awful tomorrow,
make sure you see a doctor.
Got it.
Is that the time? Already?
You can go home. I'll be fine.
I will, once you're asleep.
I'll put the key in your door's
mail slot so you can rest easy.
You'd do that?
It's fine.
I'll just play games in the meantime.
Sheesh.
I'm already laid low, so let me just say...
You were a huge help today.
Thanks.
Come on. That's just how we are.
Senpai! Senpai!
How do I beat this bald scissors dude?!
His shields explode
when I hit 'em with my blade!
Look, I'll lend you the game
and the console--just go home !
I can't go home a loser !
Will you let me sleep ?!
Sakurai!
Ami!
Is your cold all better?
Yeah, thanks. Sorry you had to cover my shift.
It's fine. I was free yesterday anyway.
Why don't I take one of your shifts, then?
I have to thank you somehow.
In that case... can you ask Hana to come?
Huh? Uzaki?
And now, a toast to Sakurai's recovery!
Cheers!
Thanks.
Korean barbecue to celebrate my recovery.
That's... a lot.
All right! It's all-you-can-eat,
and I'm grilling--so eat up, Senpai!
Salted tongue! Chuck! Tripe! Skirt!
H-hey, that's too much!
Short ribs! Knuckle! Ribeye!
Let me take my time eating!
Such energy!
She really does seem happy
that Sakurai's feeling better.
Look at you two knock 'em back!
Are beer and liquor really that tasty?
Uh-huh--especially when paired with good eats.
Let's go out for drinks when you turn 20, Hana.
Hooray!
Now that that's settled, eat up, Senpai!
You listen here...
I'm going to hit the restroom.
I'm glad you're feeling better, Sakurai.
I'm sorry I had to take the day off yesterday.
Not at all.
I'm just happy Hana took such good care of you.
So you did tell her where I live.
And? How'd it go?
"How"?
Stop pressuring me while piling
on the finest cuts of meat!
Just so you know,
it's not like that with me and Uzaki.
I want to enjoy my quiet solo lifestyle,
so I don't want people over if I can help it.
And Uzaki is basically
the polar opposite of quiet.
So gloomy!
Way gloomy!
That's what you are, Sakurai.
And what's wrong with that?!
They've really had a lot to drink...
Besides...
Uzaki may be my trusted junior,
but she's still a girl.
If rumors start at school about
her coming to my place all the time,
it'd only make unnecessary trouble for her.
I live near campus--someone could see her.
Th-This is getting complicated!
I had an inkling, but this? This is a pain!
I was fully aware, but still... still!
Dad.
Right. This'll only get juicier
if we just let it be.
It's like coffee, Ami.
Slowly roasted, painstakingly brewed...
Let's be patient and
watch over these two for now.
Yes--until we get that rich, deep flavor.
Whatcha been talkin' about?
Huh? Oh, um...
Oh, tomorrow's work.
That's right.
Aha!
We'll be getting in a shipment of beans
and other heavy packages.
Can you come in a little early, Sakurai?
Sure thing, Ami.
Thanks! It'll be so helpful
to have another man around.
Wait, what was going on just
now--between you and your dad?
Hmm... Psyching ourselves up?
Psyching--huh? What's wrong, Uzaki?
I see you call Ami by her first name.
Huh?
If I use her last name,
she'll get mixed up with her father.
Hmm. If you say so.
Hey, uh, I was really careful grilling that.
Come on!
Wait, uh... Uzaki!
Mmm! Perfect with a side of rice!
Why the hell would Uzaki want to meet me here?
She did start acting weird
in the middle of that dinner...
Did I do something to tick her off?
Senpai.
Huh?
Eh?
Keep your eye on this five-yen coin.
You're getting very sleepy-- very sleepy...
Hypnosis? Now what's she trying to pull?
You will do what I say--do what I say...
I don't know what she's after,
but she did take care of me earlier...
Oh, well. I'll play along.
Wow, I sure am feeling sleepy.
All right! Simple people really
are the easiest to hypnotize!
Who are you calling "simple," dammit?
Okay, then, Senpai!
Here we go. I just hope it's nothing unreasonable.
Call me by my first name!
Huh? Is that it?
That's what she hypnotized me for?
She's waiting for it. I guess I have to.
Ha... Ha... Ha...
Ha...?
This is a little embarrassing.
Ha... Hani.
Huh? That's not it.
Hanu.
No.
Hane.
Not that.
Hano.
Are you doing this on purpose?
Dammit!
Hana.
Again!
Yes! Again!
Hana.
Again!
Couple of love-dummies.
Hana.
Love-dumb, huh?
Again!
Love-dumb.
Hana.
So that's how it works.
I'm pretty happy with it!
It went so well--I might just
have a knack for hypnosis!
No way.
But if that's all it takes to make her happy...
Okay! Next...
"Next"?
Let's have you buy me something to drink!
Yes.
And ice cream from the convenience store!
Hey, now.
I can have you buy me lunch at the dining hall!
Don't...
Oh! And you can buy me
the latest VR setup, too--
Don't push your luck!
Ow!
No fair pretending to be hypnotized!
Says the girl making demands
of a hypnotized guy!
What are you trying to accomplish?!
I mean...
You call Ami by her first name, right?
I've known you for a pretty long time,
and I just get "Hey" and "Look here."
Rude way to treat someone, don't you think?
I see. I didn't even realize
that I'd made you feel bad.
I apologize for that. I'm sorry.
But I'm kind of, uh... I'm uncomfortable
calling girls by their first names.
Ami told me to call her that for work,
and I've been doing my best, but...
Please, just... not that.
That's fine, then. I don't want
to force you, poor gloomy thing.
Thanks.
Still, hypnotizing with a
five-yen coin in this day and age?
No way is that gonna work. Right?
Guh...
It worked! Are you kidding me?!
You must have zero resistance!
Hey! C'mon!
Buh...
How do I put her back?!
It's gotta be in here somewhere!
Uzaki!
Uzaki is floating in the sky.
It's not working.
I told you: I'm not hypnotized!
It's truly frightening that you can't remember.
Look, I'm not hypnotized, all right?
It'd be a big deal if I were!
Why do you sound ticked off?
I'm not ticked off.
Dad... could this be?
Yes...
They say you can't hypnotize
someone who doesn't trust you.
Which means these two...
It certainly looks that way.
Let's not tell them. It's too amusing.
If I were ticked off, it'd be a big deal.
You really suck at this!
What should we do, Senpai?