Sakurai Shinichi started working for us
part-time last year.
Thuggish looks aside,
he treats his work very seriously, and our regulars
have nothing but good things to say about him.
But, most importantly of all,
he's got some
mighty fine collarbones.
Whoopsie-daisy.
He's sure got the stuff.
Upon closer inspection, he's pretty hunky.
He looks nice and slender,
but he's actually pretty buff!
Sakurai, we'd like to settle the bill.
On my way!
I doubt he's noticed yet,
but he's been attracting a lot of fans.
You're pretty tall, Sakurai!
How many centimetres?
One-eighty.
Whoa, that's tall!
Do you play any sports?
I used to be in the swimming club.
Wow, really?
Swimming team, hip-hip hooray!
You've got a detective's hunch, ma'am!
And while swimming, everything is laid bare...
With all these little tidbits
I'm picking up during work,
I'd say that's progress ahoy, baby!
Your heart doesn't seem to be into it today, Ami.
Eh?
It's fine to get lost in thought sometimes,
but remember that you're on the clock.
It's important to stay on top of things
in this line of work.
You'll lose track of all kinds of things
if you aren't careful.
Right. I'm sorry.
I understand your hobbies,
but focus on work for now.
Now, go clear those customers' table.
Sure, Dad.
Dad might seem nice and gentle,
but he's pretty strict with family.
Oh deary me, I can't act like this during work.
Especially not when sharing a shift with Sakurai.
Hiya!
Ugh, you again?
Don't have anything better to do?
Right back at ya! but hey,
props to you for working on a Sunday!
Who's this? Who? Who?!
Good afternoon, Hana.
Dad knows her, too?
Sir! Up top! Yay!
Yay!
And he's just playing along with her?!
Our peak hour's just ended,
so you can sit wherever you'd like.
Thanksies!
Um... who's that?
You mean Uzaki?
She's a sophomore at our college.
Huh, she's in college?
Oh, right, Sakurai! I brought that game you lent me.
Cool. What's your thoughts?
They're lending out each other's stuff.
They must be pretty good friends.
Whew, that final act was a real thrill.
I thought it was a stand-alone title at first,
but when I found out it's actually
a sequel to some older game?
Man, I got crazy goosebumps!
I know, right?
I would've been plenty happy
if it were a plain ol' building game,
but when it turned out to be such a gem,
I knew I had to get it out there!
They seem to be getting along pretty well.
No... There's no way...
Oh, these two?
What's with the chuckle?
Oh, it's nothing.
Bring her some water, would you?
Welcome.
Ah, thanks!
So we go to the same college, huh?
I'm Asai Ami. I'm in my senior year.
Oh, really? Then that makes you Sakurai's senior!
Be right back. I'm gonna stick this
in my bag real quick.
Sure.
I'm Uzaki Hana, and I'm a sophomore!
Now that I've taken a closer look at her,
this girl's an absolute cutie!
She's got such a friendly smile...
She's pretty small, too.
Almost like a cute little animal...
Christ on a bike, that part ain't like a little animal!
This girl's no li'l critter—she's an absolute beast!
No, no, you gotta pull yourself together!
You two seem to get along really well.
Hmm? Oh, yeah, we do!
How long have you known each other?
We were in the same club in high school.
The water on Uzaki's table
is getting pretty low.
He's always been that gloomy kid
in the back of class everyone avoids!
Getting to know him was no easy feat.
He's not much different even now,
always one block away from Loner's Lane!
So I figured I'd look out for him.
Ah! So that's how it is.
Huh?
Well, call me over when
you're ready to order, Hana.
'Kay!
Well?
She's showing real promise.
You want to stick your nose in their business,
But you also feel you shouldn't interfere...
They just make you want to watch over them.
I get that.
Don't you love customer-facing jobs?
You get to watch all kinds of people
and how they live their lives, like these two.
It's one of the thrills of this business.
Uzaki. Water.
That's co-o-old!
What'd you bump into me for?!
That's what I'd like to ask you!
You're a customer! You're supposed to
leave waiting to us waiters!
What's this nonsense? You don't even
treat me like a customer half the time!
Oh, shut it!
They put on quite a show, don't you think?
You're telling me.
Looks like I'll be taking more shifts soon.
Oh, give them a towel.
What?!
Sakurai's out with a cold?
He called this morning.
I made him take the day off.
First the ice-water drenching incident,
followed by a very cold night straight after...
Well, huh. So much for the "I lift, bro" look.
He's surprisingly fragile.
Oh, yeah—I lift, bro.
So why's she still all chipper?
In that case, sir...
Man, I have been knocked down flat.
I don't remember colds hitting quite this hard.
Should I go to a doctor? Get some medicine?
Probably best if I eat something first.
But I can't move.
Now what?
What a racket. Who's there? Dammit...
And with me barely managing to get out of bed...
Hiya!
All you really out flat with a cold?
Well, I'm paying you a visit!
U-Uzaki?
What... how did you...
Are you okay, Sakurai?!
Hey, uh... Sakurai!
That must be one bad cold.
Sure is.
Well, looks like I let her into my place after all.
So, who told her where I live?
Oh? I shouldn't have?
Since I now know where he lives,
I figured we'd play games or something.
Now that's some misplaced excitement.
He looks like he's having a really bad time.
That cold must be really rough if it's
got him down like that despite his stamina.
That does it.
Have you seen a doctor?
No... can't really move.
Got any medicine?
Nope. Didn't think to get any before.
So you haven't eaten either then, huh?
Oh, well. Leave lunch to me!
Uh...
Oof...
Based on his symptoms, I'd say it's probs this one.
A cold—that calls for leeks!
Can you sit up, Sakurai?
Yeah.
Then eat a little, even if it's only a few bites.
Wow.
I've been busting my ass off, I'll have you know!
Empty fridge, awkward kitchen...
Here you go. Say "ah"!
I-I can feed myself.
Stop that!
It's good.
Right?!
Honestly... I can't really taste anything right now.
But... it's probably good.
"Probably", huh?
I'll take it.
Sorry.
See? My cooking is totally edible.
Eating really warmed me up.
You got a good sweat going on!
And now?
Strip!
I refuse.
No way! Wipe yourself down and change your clothes!
That sweat? It stinks!
It's fine! I'm just going to
take my medicine and go to sleep!
Hey! No fighting back, sickie!
You've got nice skin, mister. I'll be gentle!
Drop the weird roleplay!
Forget feeling self-conscious, now!
You must be used to being
half-naked from swim club.
I'll do the front myself!
How can being cared for be so tiring?
Here's your medicine. Take this
and you'll be all better in the morning.
But if you're still feeling awful tomorrow,
make sure you see a doctor.
Got it.
Is it that time already?
You can go home. I'll be fine.
I will, once you're asleep.
I'll chuck the key back in through
the mail slot, so you can rest easy.
You'd do that?
It's fine.
I'll just play games in the meantime.
Sheesh.
I'm already laid low, so let me just say...
You were a huge help today.
Thanks.
Come on. That's just how we are.
Sakurai! Sakurai!
How do I beat this bald scissors dude?!
His shields explode
when I hit 'em with my blade!
Look, I'll lend you the game and the console,
so just go home already!
I can't go home a loser!
Will you let me sleep?!
Sakurai!
Ami!
Is your cold all better?
Yeah, thanks. Sorry you had to cover my shift.
Don't mention it. I was free anyway.
Why don't take I take one of your shifts, then?
I've gotta thank you one way or another.
If you want to thank me...
Would you mind inviting Hana?
Huh? Uzaki?
And now, a toast to Sakurai's recovery!
Cheers!
Thanks.
Celebrating my recovery with Korean barbecue...
This'll lay heavy on my stomach.
C'mon! It's all-you-can-eat,
and I'm the grill girl, so eat up, Sakurai!
Salted tongue! Chuck! Tripe! Skirt!
H-Hey, you're piling on too much!
Short ribs! Knuckle! Ribeye!
Let me take my time!
So full of energy!
She's happy as a clam now that Sakurai's all better.
Look at you two knock 'em back!
Are beer and liquor really that tasty?
Uh-huh, especially with good food on your plate.
Let's go drinking one day once you're twenty, Hana.
Hooray!
And with that sorted, eat up, Sakurai!
Now. Listen. Here!
I'm gonna hit up the ladies' room.
I'm glad you're feeling better, Sakurai.
Sorry that I had to take the day off yesterday.
Oh no, don't worry.
I'm just happy Hana took such good care of you.
So you really did tell her my address...
Well? How'd it go?
How did what go?
Please don't pressure me by piling
my plate with the finest cuts of meat.
Just so you know, it's not like that between us.
I just want to enjoy a quiet solo life,
so I'd rather not have to
entertain guests if I can help it.
And Uzaki is the antithesis of "quiet".
Gloomy!
Way gloomy!
That's what you are, Sakurai.
And what's wrong with that?!
They've been drinking themselves silly.
Besides...
Uzaki may be my trusted junior,
but she's still a girl.
It'd cause nothing but unnecessary trouble for her
if rumour spread of her coming to my place often.
I live near campus,
and you never know who's watching.
Th-This is getting complicated!
I had an inkling, but this? This is dreadful!
Yet he's so attentive of her! Overbearingly attentive!
Dad.
Right. It'd be best if we didn't
pluck this one until it has ripened.
It's like coffee, Ami.
Roasted slowly, painstakingly brewed...
Let's bide our time and
continue watching over these two.
Yes—until we reach that rich, deep flavour.
Whatcha all chatting 'bout?
Huh? Oh, well...
Oh, we were discussing work for tomorrow.
That's right.
Aha!
A shipmeant of beans and other
heavy packages will be arriving,
so do you think you can
come in a bit early, Sakurai?
Sure thing, Ami.
Thanks! It'll help a lot to have
another pair of muscles around.
Sure, but what was that just now
between you and your dad?
Hmm... Just psyching ourselves up?
Psyching up, you say...
Hmm? What's up, Uzaki?
I see you call Ami by her first name.
Huh?
If I use her last name,
she'll get mixed up with her father.
Hmm. If you say so.
Hey, uh, I was really careful grilling that.
Come on!
Wait, uh... Uzaki!
Mhm! Perfect with a side of rice!
Why the hell would Uzaki want to meet me here?
She's been acting weird ever since
we went out for dinner.
Did I piss her off somehow?
Sakurai.
Huh?
Eh?
Keep your eyes on this five-yen coin.
You're getting sleepy, very sleepy...
Hypnosis? The hell is she tryna pull?
You will do anything I say, anything I say...
I dunno what she's trying to accomplish, but I guess
I do owe her for taking care of me back then.
Whatever. Guess I'll play along.
Wow, I sure am feeling sleepy all of a sudden.
Score! Simple people really are
the easiest to hypnotize!
Who are you calling "simple", you bastard?
Okay then, Sakurai!
Here we go. I just hope it's nothing unreasonable.
Call me by my first name!
Huh? That's it?
She'd hypnotise me for something this trivial?
She's waiting for it. Guess I'll have to.
Ha... Ha... Ha...
Ha...?
This is a little embarrassing.
Ha... Hani.
Huh? That's not it.
Hanu.
No.
Hane.
Not that.
Hano.
Are you messing with me?
Goddammit!
Hana.
Again!
Yes! Again!
Hana.
Again!
Couple of love-dummies.
Hana.
Love-dumb, huh?
Again!
Love-dumb.
Hana.
Now, that's the stuff. I'm satisfied for now.
Man, that went better than expected.
I might be a natural at this!
You're not.
But if that's all it takes to cheer her up...
Okay! Next...
"Next"?
Let's have you buy me a drink!
Yes.
And ice cream from the convenience store!
Hey, now.
I can have you buy me lunch at the dining hall!
Don't...
Oh! And you can buy me the latest VR setup, too—
Don't push your luck!
Ouch!
Faking your hypnosis is dirty!
Says the girl making demands through hypnosis!
What are you trying to pull?
I mean...
You call Ami by her first name, right?
I've known you for a pretty long time,
yet all I get is a "Hey" and a "Listen up here".
Kinda rude, don't you think?
I see. I hadn't realised that
what I was doing was upsetting you.
I apologise for that. I'm sorry.
But I'm kind of, uh... uncomfortable
calling girls by their first names.
Ami's forced it onto me for work,
so I've been trying, but...
Please, just anything but that.
That's fine, then. I wouldn't want to force
a misery guts like you to do my bidding.
Thanks.
Still, hypnotizing with a
five-yen coin in this day and age?
You didn't think that'd actually work, right?
Guh...
It worked! Are you kidding me?!
You must have zero resistance!
Hey! Snap out of it!
Buh...
How do I reverse this?!
It's gotta cover that somewhere in here, right?
Uzaki!
Uzaki is flying through the sky.
It's not working.
I told you: I wasn't hypnotised!
It's legit scary that you can't remember.
It didn't happen, okay?
Rather, I'd be impressed if it did!
What's with the attitude?
I don't have an attitude.
Dad... could this be?
Yes...
Word goes that hypnosis doesn't work
on people who don't trust you.
Which means these two...
It certainly appears that way.
Let's not tell them. It's too amusing.
If I had an attitude, it'd be a travesty.
You bloody suck at this!
What should we do, Sakurai?