"Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out!"
"Episode 9: Tsuki Uzaki Wants a Thrill?"
You're a real upstanding guy, Senpai.
"Tsuki Uzaki - 43"
Welcome! Is this your senior at college, Hana?
She's told me all about you!
"Cue one weird red flag"
"The dawning of various realizations"
"The misunderstanding quietly grows deeper"
"Uzaki F T W"
"Lottery Ticket"
"One draw per ticket"
"Uza Shopping District Association"
"Gettin' Crabby in the Crab Prefecture"
"Welcome to Tottori Sand Dunes Conan Airport!
--Gosho Aoyama"
"Café Poirot"
Wow, they really went
all out in the airport, huh?
"Café Poirot"
I hate to ask this now...
What's up?
"Tottori Sand Dunes Conan Airport"
"Case Closed Location Guide"
This is my first time in Tottori!
Hey, Senpai, your eyes are
totally different. They're kinder!
"Case Closed Location Guide"
Oh, shut up!
Hey, those glasses actually make you look, uh...
"Episode 10: I Want to Hang Out in Tottori!"
But why Tottori?
Well, you see, Asai...