Shinichi Sakurai: 19-year-old college sophomore
Hana Uzaki: 18-year-old college freshman
Spring
Summer
Fall
Winter
Spring once again
Shinichi Sakurai: 20-year-old college junior
Hana Uzaki: 19-year-old college sophomore
Episode 1
Uzaki Wants to Hang Out!
Schedule Updates
Faculty
Status
Course Name
Classroom
School of Law
School of
Information Sciences
School of Philosophy
School of Law
School of Education
Moved
Cancelled
Electoral Systems I - The Rational Politician
Fundamentals of Quantitative Finance
History of Western Philosophy (Practical)
Art History (Practical II)
Electoral Systems I - The Rational Politician
Fundamentals of Quantitative Finance
History of Western Philosophy (Practical)
Art History (Practical II)
Analytic Tools of Institutional Theory (3)
Game Theory and Collective Action Theory
8th Annual Seminar: Theory and Design of College Education
Having your nose
pulled up really hurts
Kuso Cat: The Purrce Awakens / English
###############################
Nyaventures: The Kuso Cat War / English
##############################
Golden Catnap / Japanese
##########################
One Million Yen Kuso Cat / Japanese
##############################
Underdog, the Tiger, and the Fish / Japanese
#################################
The Godmeowther / Japanese
Sold out
Computer and
Cellphone Accessories
LO
H I
She's just sitting in a massage chair
No, really. We told you she's just sitting a massage chair
She's just sitting a massage chair, okay?
Totally oblivious
VR Gear Demo
TANEDA RAMEN
Epi
sode
Mr. Manager
Epi
Episode 2
Mr. Manager
Wants to Sneak a Peek!