Now, that's a sight that gives you spring vibes.
Sakurai!
Huh?
Uzaki, right?
Yup, Uzaki Hana!
Looks like I'll be
your junior again this year!
Here's to a great year!
Huh? You won't be swimming in college?
Nope. They don't even have
a swim club here to begin with.
What a shame after keeping it up
through high school.
Ah, what's it matter?
There's plenty stuff to do in college.
Sakurai...
Y-Yep, there sure is.
Or so I thought.
Oh, Sakurai!
What the...
What in the...
What in the what?
What in the what?!
I kinda figured he'd keep this up all year.
Sakurai!
Whoops!
Overshot you!
Uzaki, right?
All alone again today, aren't we?
Well then, guess I've
gotta hang out with you!
Your college loner
lifestyle ends today!
What you wanna do for lunch?
Mhm... Let's check out the dining hall, I guess.
Oh, mind if we tag along?
Cancelled, huh?
Looks like I have a free afternoon today.
Sakurai!
I don't have work today, either.
What to do, what to do...
Eek!
What's with that glare?
S-Scary...
Sakurai!
Guess I'll just go out and about for once.
Not like I often get to enjoy peace
and quiet with her around, after all.
Sakurai, Sakurai, Sakurai, Sakurai!
How many times do I have to tell you to stop yelling?
How many times do I have to tell you to stop yel
ling?
I kept calling you, but you just wouldn't respond!
So, where ya headed today, Sakurai?
What the hell do you think you're doing, dumbass?
Oh, going out for lunch today?
Aw, too bad.
My friends and I already ate.
But if you insist, I'd be fine with watching you eat.
I've got no classes this afternoon.
I'm just going out for a stroll.
Later.
What are you following me for, Uzaki?
Wow, you look pissed.
Well, as it turns out,
I'm suddenly free this afternoon, too.
Given half the chance,
I know you'll do the old loner thing.
And two's gotta be way more fun than one!
Mind your own business.
Besides, haven't I told you a million times
that I'd much rather some peace and quiet?
Here we go again. Being a loner is no fun!
Stop calling me that.
Good point, you're no loner! I'm with you!
Quit tagging along, you damn pest!
Feeling shy?
Like hell!
So, where are we going?
Not telling.
Karaoke? Bowling?
Aw, tell me!
Hell, no.
Ugh!
What are you acting so cold for?
Not in the mood today.
Not in the mood?
What's the deal? You had no problem
hanging out with me before!
Huh?
You just treat me however you fancy!
Am I just a convenient woman to
have around when you're in the mood?!
Stop spouting junk that's so easy to misunderstand!
Enemy of womankind.
Utter trash.
Scum.
Fine! Suit yourself!
Tag along if you must!
Hooray!
Hey, let's go get food after we're done.
I'll gladly sit with you for dinner!
I ain't paying.
Aw, cheapskate.
So you were trying to sponge off of me!
Wait, were you gonna
watch a movie by yourself today?
Huh? Yeah.
Going solo!
What's so funny about that?
Going solo to the movies!
Doesn't get much lonelier than that!
What's next, solo BBQ? Solo sushi-go-round?
Shut up for once, would you?
You'll make an enemy out of everyone.
At least quiet down a little.
Listen up, we're in the age of the individual.
We all want to find time in our busy lives
to watch a movie the way we like it.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Shouldn't everyone be free to enjoy
their free time however they want?
Don't laugh off different hobbies
just because your standards differ.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Not everyone feels the need to plan when
or with whom to watch a movie in advance.
That's just how it is.
I see.
Spoken like a true loner!
Can I wallop her just once?
Anyone can go watch a movie alone
whenever they feel like it.
Throw others into the mix
and scheduling can become a headache.
I see.
But you can't talk about spoilers loudly
with your friends afterwards if you go alone!
That's one of the absolute worst things you can do!
It's okay.
I get it.
You're determined to soldier on alone
despite your loneliness.
Don't give me that affectionate look!
Honestly.
I knew I shouldn't have brought you.
I was gonna tail you all sneaky-peeky-like
if push came to shove, anyway.
What's your deal?
Is that your idea of fun?
Huh?
Well, it'd be funny if I spotted you
going into some weird store or something!
I know I'd laugh myself silly
if I saw you buying dirty DVDs!
Ow! Ow!
Ow, ow, ow!
Sakurai, I... Sakurai! Sakurai!
I give up! I give up!
You, as a college student, are an adult!
So start acting like one and stop prying into
other people's hobbies or private lives!
Sorry! I'm sorry!
Sheesh.
I haven't even had time to pick a movie
with you all up in my business.
You came without a movie in mind?
It was a last-minute thing.
Besides, picking something on a whim
is one of the thrills of going solo.
Oh, is it, now?
Uzaki.
Yes?
Got anything you wanna watch? It's on me.
Huh, really? What happened to going solo?
Not like I have to go solo.
If anything, it'd be a dick move
to go on my merry way.
I could probably cover for two
with my membership card.
Seriously?!
Well, if you insist, I'll let you treat me!
Thanks!
Let's see...
This one!
What a bargain! Heroes as far as the eye can see!
Ooh, that's a great one.
I've seen it before, but what's another watch?
Huh!
For two college students, please. I'll be using points.
Certainly. One moment.
She has her moments, but maybe I went a bit too far.
Seems she's happy to get treated,
so I guess we're even now.
By the way, Sakurai...
You've saved up enough points by yourself
to cover someone else's ticket?
That's honestly kinda sad.
She has the nerve to say stuff
like that after I pay for her?
You're, like, a professional loner!
Huh? Uh, wait... Sakurai?
It's just a joke! Sorry! I'm so sorry!
Yow! Stop! Stop!
Will that couple ever shut up?
That was great!
Yeah. A good film's always worth a rewatch.
All those points you banked by
going to the movies alone—gone!
That's what you found oh, so great?
Dammit. My kindness is wasted on you.
Hey, can we stop by the electronics store?
I need new earbuds.
Yeah, sure.
See, it's that kind of thing.
Huh?
What is it about these kinda stores
that make me feel I have to buy something?
Hey, nice.
Sakurai!
Yeah?
Over here! This way!
What happened to those earbuds?
C'mon, the next seat's open!
Mind listening?
Well, whatever. Might be nice after a movie.
Right?
That hits the spot!
This is nice. Real nice.
Right?
Though I usually have more trouble with
my shoulders than my back.
Shoulders?
Wha—where'd that come from?
Oh, sorry...
I can't help but make noise during a massage...
My, uh, my shoulders have always been tight—
Well, um... I-If you keep doing that...
I'd buy this on the spot if I could!
It... It just... It feels...
sooo good...
Let's get going, okay?!
We haven't even been here for five minutes!
Shut up!
S-Save that for alone time!
Save what now?
I swear, this moron.
Can't believe she'd moan like that in public.
Hey, Sakurai!
What now?
Ten minutes of standing on this,
and it's like getting a full workout!
Well?
You should give it a try, too!
Oh, my God!
You're such an idiot!
Whoa! Check it out!
What is it this time?
Look! It's VR! VR!
Huh! So this is virtual reality...
Would you like to try it out?
Yes! I wanna give it a try!
My screen turns when I turn!
VR is amazing!
This is really cool, Sakurai!
Okay, okay. You don't need to yell.
My weapon! No! Not this one!
Ammo! I'm outta ammo!
Did you check behind you?
Huh? Behind me?!
Here they come! Look at 'em all!
Your reactions are the best.
They should put you in a commer—
I died!
Wow, VR is so cool!
Er, are you all right?
I'm fine.
What's wrong, Sakurai?
Um, would your boyfriend like to have a turn?
I'm not her boyfriend.
But... okay.
Something not so dangerous.
These ocean graphics are something else!
Hey, you look like a normal person with those goggles.
They hide your mean look!
Shut it, dimwit.
Whoa!
That's huge! A giant shark!
Wait, isn't it swimming this way?
Huh? Is it?!
I-It's biting me! It's totally biting me! Yow!
You're way too scared!
You're one to talk!
Let me go! Hey!
I'm gonna get this disgraceful display
on video and tease you about it later!
Uh, miss?
Don't get too close to the player...
Just so huge!
Hmm? What's this?
A jellyfish? Octopus? Sunfish?!
It's so big. And soft!
And kind of frightening!
I never thought much of VR,
but damn! It's out of this world!
It's so powerful—and even reproduces touch!
Are you all right, Miss?
Yeah, it's okay. I'm fine.
You said VR made you want to do something physical,
and here you are, excitedly racking up a pile of strikes!
Focus!
Will you shut up for once?
C'mon, here comes the next one!
You can do it! Knock it out of the park! Home run!
That's enough out of—
That so didn't fly straight!
Dammit.
You said you did this before. You totally didn't!
You really tick me off, dammit.
I played for one year in junior high.
Ooh! I wanna try, too!
Here's my card. There's still some on there.
Thanks!
Don't stand too close or the ball will hit you.
Got it!
If I hit a home run, dinner's on you!
Eyes forward! You wanna get hurt?
Okay...
Plant the feet...
Swivel the hips...
Like the real deal.
Huh, wait. Did—
Did you stretch?
Oh.
It... It hurts...
Are you nuts, whipping out a full swing like that?!
On your back, right now!
I could feel it crack...
Yeah, I'll say!
I copied you
and look where it got me...
A novice can't just start putting
their hips into a swing!
Of course you're gonna hurt yourself, moron!
This is all your fault, Sakurai...
How so?!
Just go home and get some sleep.
And see a doctor tomorrow.
A doctor, you say?
No, I wanna go out for dinner!
Learn to give up!
Let's eat!
Since you can walk fine on your own,
it's probably nothing serious.
If it still hurts tomorrow, see a doctor.
And you really should head home now and go sleep.
I'll be fine.
Yummy-yum-yum.
You're seriously out of shape, aren't you?
A fit person wouldn't have gotten injured like that.
What did you expect? I'm just starting out!
Beginners need to warm up, at least.
Back injuries are a big deal.
Fine.
You realise that this never would've happened
if you hadn't forced your way along, ri—
Huh?
That was my chicken...
Hey.
Why are you eating it?
Huh?
When'd you manage to eat all of them?
W-We weren't sharing?
Over my dead body!
And how much do you think you're sharing?
I don't want it anymore!
Temper, temper! Your poor girlfriend!
She's not my girlfriend...
Another order of chicken, please.
Coming right up!
Your chicken's so good, my chopsticks just kept going!
Good one, missy!
Talk about a bundle of sunshine.
Here you go.
On the house. Eat up!
Wow! For real?
Oh, no, we couldn't!
Go on, it's fine!
Delish!
Honestly.
It'd be rude not to accept it, Sakurai!
Well, I guess you're right.
Okay, don't mind if I—
Why do you eat everything?!
Sorry! I didn't mean to!
Here's your chicken.
Again?!
Stingy!
Sakurai!
Good morning!
Hey.
I had fun yesterday!
What?
All you did was hurt your back.
Huh?
C'mon, it was fun not being a loner for a day, right?
I made it clear from the very beginning
that I intended to spend the day alone.
Oh, look at you, pretending you weren't happy.
Watch it.
I've never been to a batting cage with
my girlfriends before, either. That was new!
Teach me how to swing well, okay?
Next time I wanna really send it flying!
Hey, how 'bout we go again today?
I have work.
Aw.
Next time, then!
"Next time", huh?
This idiot really doesn't let a little pain
get in the way of having fun.
I don't know when she got like this...
Like this? Or like this?
Well, at least I won't be bored.
I can put up with her a little, I guess.
Yeah, next time.
Uh, Sakurai?
Hmm?
After that thing we did yesterday?
My back still hurts!
It's all your fault, y'know!
Phrasing!
It even hurts to walk! Carry me!
C'mon, it's your fault!
Shut up!
Next time we'll meet the café owner!