You think I want to be asked to hang out with you?
honto wa sasotte hoshii nante
No, no! I've never even thought about it once!
omottemo nankanai sonnakoto manzara zenzen naisu
I'm only subtly ushering you
uzagarami soremo hitotsuno
To begin considering the possibilities!
nadamesukashi negotiation
I thought I'd be nice and hear what you had planned for today
kyou no yotei kiiteageteru noni nan nan
But why would I want to come along? (Seriously, what're you imagining?)
nansuka sore (nansuka sore)
Even I think your being so serious and gloomy is super creepy!
souiu taido de korarecha watashimo nanka nanka moyarusu
Totally!
souda
Just brushing me off as annoying won't help you a lot
uzaitte omowaretatte iikotonante honrainai
But praising my blossoming body would be ideal!
demo itsuka uzakawaiitte omowarechaeba mondainai
I thought I'd just rush up some day and chatter away (why not?)
toriaezu damemoto datte koe kakechatte soshitara
And you just went along
sunnari nottekuru
With my silly whims
are kekkou choroisune
Being so distant sure seems lonely
bocchi wa itsudatte yappari samishiitte
So just stick close to me and come nearer, step by step!
kocchini oidette mouchotto mouchotto!
Even if you turn aside, step away or block my attempts
ittari kitari oshitari hiitari
I'll repeat them again, again and again without hesitation
nando nando nando kurikaesundarou
Eagerly anticipating the results!
omoi no yukue wa fumei da
Teasing you soothes, refreshes and makes me just way too happy
nadamesukashite soukai kibun tsuukai happy happy
I'm not just saying this either, I'm totally serious!
atekosuri janaissu zenbu zenbu honkissu
I want to show you how to love life's simple joys!
shinpuru ni tanoshindeimasu enjoy and joy
Let's cherish them together every day
kyouzonkyouei no rireishon
Sounds great? Right, right?
desune desune
We're just going up and down with this seesaw game
dakedo kakehiki ja seesaw game
Though irritating and whimsical, I'll always wait for you
kimayoi kimagure kimamani matteru
Ah, being asked out by you
aa sasotte hoshii nante
Was something I hadn't thought about, but it'd be so nice!
omottemo nankanai sonnakoto attara it's so nice
Teasing you, playing and horsing around would make every day nice!
karakatte tawamureatte kongaragatte have a nice day janaisu