Happy, mischevious chatter echoes through the air
itazurana kotoba ga afureru itsumo no gogo
Imbuing these mundane afternoons with it's distinctive flavour
taikutsuna mainichi ni kaze ga fuita
When I'm with you in this world filled with adventures
arifureta sekai de kimi to sugoshita jikan wa
Every second feels like a new, special find
atarimae janai kigashita
No matter how often we laugh together, I'll never grow tired of it
nando datte waraiatte
I will treasure each and every day we spend together
tanoshii hibi wo kasane
Slowly hinting at those feelings concealed deep in my chest
mune no oku ni shimaikonda omoi wo sagasuyo
These knockings against the door of my heart
kokoro no tobira wo tataiteru
First once, then twice, resound deep inside
hitotsu futatsu narihibiku nokku
My still-dormant feelings await to be roused by their prince
darenimo kikoenai mama kimochi wa nemuru
Hidden behind my bright, sunny disposition
akarui hizashi no sono ura de
My true hopes are waiting to be discovered by you
honto no koto kakurenbo shiteru
So make sure to some day!
itsuka kitto mitsuketene nantene
Just kidding