Happy, mischevious chatter echoes through the air
itazurana kotoba ga afureru itsumo no gogo
taikutsuna mainichi ni kaze ga fuita
Imbuing these mundane afternoons with its distinctive flavour
arifureta sekai de kimi to sugoshita jikan wa
When I'm with you in this world filled with adventures
atarimae janai kigashita
Every second feels like a new, special find
nando datte waraiatte
No matter how often we laugh together, I'll never grow tired of it
tanoshii hibi wo kasane
I will treasure each and every day we spend together
mune no oku ni shimaikonda omoi wo sagasuyo
Slowly hinting at those feelings concealed deep in my chest
kokoro no tobira wo tataiteru
These knockings against the door of my heart
hitotsu futatsu narihibiku nokku
First once, then twice, resound deep inside
darenimo kikoenai mama kimochi wa nemuru
My still-dormant feelings await to be roused by their prince
akarui hizashi no sono ura de
Hidden behind my bright, sunny disposition
honto no koto kakurenbo shiteru
My true hopes are waiting to be discovered by you
itsuka kitto mitsuketene nantene
So make sure to some day!
Just kidding!